<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<!--
 Copyright (c) 2011-2014 Microsoft Mobile. All rights reserved.

 Nokia, Nokia Connecting People, Nokia Developer, and HERE are trademarks
 and/or registered trademarks of Nokia Corporation. Other product and company
 names mentioned herein may be trademarks or trade names of their respective
 owners.

 See the license text file delivered with this project for more information.

-->
<restaurant>
    <info>
        <name>diner</name>
        <logo>content/logo.png</logo>
        <address>
            <street>1567 Broadway</street>
            <city>New York</city>
            <country>United States</country>
            <coordinates>
                <latitude>40.75930175423635</latitude>
                <longitude>-73.98525953292847</longitude>
            </coordinates>
        </address>
        <map>
            <minZoomLevel>12</minZoomLevel>
            <maxZoomLevel>17</maxZoomLevel>
        </map>
        <telephone>+2129189999</telephone>
        <url>http://www.diner.com</url>
        <description>It takes guts to open a restaurant in Times Square that lacks a theme or strives to be classier than a carnival. Granted, Diner offers an audacious voyeur's paradise in its soaring staircase that rises alongside a suspended abstract sculpture of a fork. Mayson Bacon Jr. has succeeded finding a perfect balance between class and bacon.</description>
    </info>    
    <menu>
        <category id="category1" name="Soups" icon="content/soups_icon.png">
            <dish name="The King of Prawns" icon="">Deep-fried king prawns and Sweet Chili sauce.</dish>
            <dish name="Super Hot Jalapeno Pops" icon="">Deep-fried jalapenos filled with cheese. Served with garlic mayonnaise and out SuperHot Chilisauce.</dish>
            <dish name="Muchos Nachos" icon="">Tortillaa chips, melted cheddar cheese, salsa sauce, jalapeno slices, sour cream &amp; guacamole.</dish>
            <dish name="Just Fries" icon="">Salted fries with bbq sauce.</dish>
            <dish name="Blue Cheese 'n Fries" icon="">Seasoned Criss Cuts with blue cheese sauce.</dish>
            <dish name="Sweet Fries" icon="">Sweet potato fries with our special mustard sauce.</dish>
        </category>
        <category id="category2" name="Vegetarian" icon="content/vegetarian_icon.png">
            <dish name="THE Ceasar Salad" icon="">A mixed green salad with Caesar dressing, Parmesan cheese, croutons and arugula with a choice of chicken breast, marinated shrimps, bacon or chevre.</dish>
            <dish name="All Vegs" icon="">A mixed green salad with cherry tomato, cucumber, fresh pineapple, orange, marinated red onion, watermelon, arugula &amp;  deep-fried spring rolls. Served with ranch dressing, toasted bread and Sweet Chili sauce.</dish>
            <dish name="Fruity Fish Salad" icon="">A mixed green salad with salmon fillet, cherry tomato, cucumber, fresh pineapple, orange, marinated red onion, watermelon, lime &amp; arugula.  Oil &amp; herb dressing and toasted bread.</dish>
        </category>
        <category id="category3" name="Sea Food" icon="content/sea_food_icon.png">
            <dish name="Fish of the day" icon="">Whatever fish comes up, served with seasonal vegetables and Tartar sauce.</dish>
            <dish name="Tons of Tuna" icon="">A huge steak of fresh tuna, baked sweet potato and lime mayo.</dish>
        </category>
        <category id="category4" name="Steaks" icon="content/steaks_icon.png">
            <dish name="Giant BBQ Steak" icon="">A 250g sirloin steak, fries, seasonal veggies and BBQ mayo.</dish>
            <dish name="Surf 'n Turf" icon="">A 180g sirloin steak, deep-fried king prawns, bell pepper, asparagus, red onion, whiskey- and Bearnaise sauce, Criss Cuts and garnished with arugula.</dish>
            <dish name="Silence of the Lambs" icon="">Lamb Loin Chops with minty mushed peas, country fries and creamy mustard sauce.</dish>
            <dish name="Latino Chick" icon="">Chicken breast with Latino sauce and salad of cherry tomatos, cucumber, marinated red onion &amp; arugula. Fresh pineapple, garlic mayonnaise and Criss Cuts.</dish>
        </category>
        <category id="category5" name="Desserts" icon="content/desserts_icon.png">
            <dish name="Master Muffin" icon="">Chocolate muffin with white-chock chips, served with vanilla whipped cream.</dish>
            <dish name="The Big Apple" icon="">Apple pie with pecan nuts and raisins, served with vanilla ice cream and chocolate sauce.</dish>
            <dish name="Shake it, shake it" icon="">A giant milk shake with a choice of banana-chocolate, chocolate, strawberry-vanilla or mint-chocolate. Made with real fruits and choc.</dish>
            <dish name="Super Cheesecake" icon="">A home made cheesecake served with heaps of whipped cream and Goji-berry &amp; strawberry sauces.</dish>
        </category>
        <category id="category5" name="Drinks" icon="content/drinks_icon.png">
            <dish name="Master Muffin" icon="">Chocolate muffin with white-chock chips, served with vanilla whipped cream.</dish>
            <dish name="The Big Apple" icon="">Apple pie with pecan nuts and raisins, served with vanilla ice cream and chocolate sauce.</dish>
            <dish name="Shake it, shake it" icon="">A giant milk shake with a choice of banana-chocolate, chocolate, strawberry-vanilla or mint-chocolate. Made with real fruits and choc.</dish>
            <dish name="Super Cheesecake" icon="">A home made cheesecake served with heaps of whipped cream and Goji-berry &amp; strawberry sauces.</dish>
        </category>
    </menu>
</restaurant>
